Let go of what you know. Let go of what you fear. Hold on to what you need.
Love and Honor is a drama, romance film directed by Danny Mooney.
When a young soldier in Vietnam gets dumped by his hometown girl, he and his best
friend decide to go AWOL and return to the States to win her back.
Mickey Wright, played by Liam Hemsworth.
Dalton Joiner, played by Austin Stowell.
Candace, played by Teresa Palmer.
Juniper / Jane, played by Aimee Teegarden.
Peter, played by Chris Lowell.
Topher, played by Wyatt Russell.
Love and Honor is a 2013 romantic drama film directed by Danny Mooney.
It is Mooney's feature-film directorial debut.
The film, based on a true story of a Michigan soldier, takes place during the
Vietnam War and is set in Ann Arbor and surrounding areas.
The story follows a soldier who, after being dumped by his girlfriend, decides to
return home secretly from war with his best friend to win her back.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, police
brutality, u.s. soldier, anti war, awol.
The tone is dark and emotional.